<resources>
    <string name="app_name">qestion1</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="XXI">The first word found by researchers similar to poker was
found in the English dictionary of the XVII century.</string>
    <string name="Americans">According to researchers, the most gambling nation on the planet are
     Americans</string>
    <string name="sochial_status">Initially, each suit corresponded to a specific social
     a group of citizens</string>
    <string name="difrient_game">Today, more than 130 varieties of poker games are already known
    </string>

    <string name="five_mastchi">In the late forties , card manufacturers tried to add more
three suits</string>
    <string name="people">According to sociological research, about 75% of people on the planet
        they continue to claim that poker is a gambling game, that is, winning in their opinion
        it does not depend on the level of professionalism and training of the player.</string>
    <string name="q1">In poker, there is a hand called a ‘dead man’s hand’ consisting of two aces
        and two eights, and it is given this name because it is the hand Wild Bill Hickok had when
        he was shot in the back of the head by Jack McCall.</string>
    <string name="q2">“Anna Kournikova” is a hand in Poker that “looks better than it plays”.</string>
    <string name="q3">Richard Nixon was an excellent poker player. He was so good that his first
        campaign for the House of Representatives was mostly funded by poker winnings from his time
        in the navy.</string>
    <string name="q4">Pro poker player Tom Dwan started playing online poker with the $50 his dad
        gave him for his birthday and earned over $5,000,000 by the next 3-4 years.</string>
    <string name="q5">Two men were brought up on federal hacking charges when they exploited a bug
        in video poker machines and won half a million dollars. His lawyer argued, “All these guys
        did is simply push a sequence of buttons that they were legally entitled to push.” The case
        was dismissed.</string>
    <string name="q6">Andrei Karpov was so desperate to stay in a poker game, he put his wife up
        as a stake after he’d run out of money. He then lost. She was so angry she left him for the
        winner.</string>

    <string name="true_button">True</string>
    <string name="false_button">False</string>
</resources>